# Aizaz Jamil

### **Technologies**

HTML, Pug CSS3, Sass/Scss/Less Bootstrap 3,4 **JavaScript** iQuery Github React Js (Beginner) PSD to HTML WordPress Responsive Design **Photoshop** HTML Email

### Software

Visual Studio Code Sublime Text Atom

#### **Education**

Govt. College Asghar Mall (ICS) Computer Science

### Personal

Email: aizaz-jamil28@outlook.com

Mobile: +92 348 5552127

Status: Single

Address: H1-347 Muslim Town Kurri Road Sadigabad, Rawalpindi, Pakistan

CNIC No: 37402-6597009-3

#### Information

Urdu English

### **Training Program**

React Js

## **Summary**

My name is Aizaz Jamil. I'm a self-taught Front-end UI developer based in Pakistan. I have 2+ years of industry experience working with companies and Independently. I partner with design teams to execute and build beautiful, progressive Web user interfaces, with a strong focus on responsive design, performance, and accessibility, using the latest front-end design techniques.

## **Professional Experience**

### AiiMS - Discover Your Uniqueness

### Front-End Developer

09/2019 - Present

- Used HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap3/4, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass/Scss, Flexbox, Css Grid and Js Libraries.
- Converts PSDs into hand-coded HTML/CSS.
- Strong knowledge of front-end technologies including HTML5, JQuery, Bootstrap, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Created and implemented a custom CSS flexbox system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.
- Worked on cross-browser compatibility.

### **Digital Poin8**

### Front-End Developer

08/2019 - Present

- Used HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap3/4, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass/Scss, PostCss, WordPress and Js Libraries.
- Converts PSDs into hand-coded HTML/CSS.
- Strong knowledge of front-end technologies including HTML5, JQuery, Bootstrap, CSS3, JavaScript and WordPress
- Created and implemented a custom CSS flexbox system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.
- Worked on cross-browser compatibility.

### **Ark Techno Solutions**

### **Front-End Developer**

12/2017 - 07/2019

- Used HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap3/4, JavaScript, JQuery, Sass/Scss, PostCss and Js Libraries.
- Converts PSDs into hand-coded HTML/CSS.
- Strong knowledge of front-end technologies including HTML5, JQuery, Bootstrap, CSS3, JavaScript.
- Created and implemented a custom CSS flexbox system, with CSS media queries for mobile responsiveness.
- Worked on cross-browser compatibility.